https://www.sphinxdateranch.com/privacy-policy

Menu
PantryArizona Wine & BeerDrinks, Coffee & TeaHoneys, Jams & SpreadsOils & DressingsFlour, Pasta & GrainsNative Arizona FoodsPrickly Pear FruitSalsas & SaucesSnack FoodsSpices & SaltsSweets & CandiesSphinx Date Co. OriginalsDatesDate GiftsMedjool DatesSpecialty VarietiesDried Fruit & NutsBulk Dried FruitsBulk Premium NutsGifts, Tins & TraysSnacks & Trail MixesGiftsArizona Gift BasketsBeer & Wine Gift BasketsDried Fruit & Nuts GiftsMother's Day Gift BasketsArizona WineArizona WineBeer & Wine Gift Baskets
Visit Us
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Please note we use cookies to help improve our product and service. Sphinx Date Co. and Google serves cookies to analyse traffic to this site.
Information about your use of our site is shared with Google for that purpose.
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, Statement of Privacy
This is the website of SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com
Our postal address is 3039 N. Scottsdale RoadScottsdale, AZ 85251
We can be reached via e-mail at info@sphinxdateranch.comor you can reach us by telephone at (800) 482-3283
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, Web site and governs data collection and usage at all SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, Statement of Privacy. SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Collection of your Personal Information
As an E-commerce Web site, SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, Web site.
Use of your Personal Information
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested. It is possible that SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, and its affiliates. SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SPHINX RANCH LLC, including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, or the public.
Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control your Personal Information
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences by emailing info@sphinxdateranch.com. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records. You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.
Security of your Personal Information
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we use a secure payment gateway so your information is protected.
Changes to this Statement
SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, will use your personal information, SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SPHINX RANCH LLC, dba SphinxDateRanch.com, is protecting your information.
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that
you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change
this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure
that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this
request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
Copyright © 2019 Sphinx Ranch, LLC. All rights reserved.
